{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Name the former spouses of these celebrities. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Brad Pitt",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Jennifer Aniston - 2000-2005"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nicole Kidman",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Tom Cruise - 1990-2001"
  }, {
    "answer": "Katie Holmes",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Tom Cruise - 2006-2012"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ashton Kutcher",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Demi Moore - 2005-2013"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bruce Willis",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Demi Moore - 1987-2000"
  }, {
    "answer": "Angelina Jolie",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Billy Bob Thornton - 2000-2003"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lisa Marie Presley",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Michael Jackson - 1994-1996"
  }, {
    "answer": "Madonna",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Sean Penn - 1985-1989"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jessica Simpson",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Nick Lachey - 2002-2006"
  }, {
    "answer": "Kevin Federline",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Britney Spears - 2004-2007"
  }, {
    "answer": "Guy Ritchie",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Madonna - 2000-2008"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tommy Lee",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Pamela Anderson - 1995-1998"
  }, {
    "answer": "Reese Witherspoon",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Ryan Phillippe - 1999-2007"
  }, {
    "answer": "Paul McCartney",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Heather Mills - 2002-2008"
  }, {
    "answer": "Richard Burton",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Elizabeth Taylor - 1964-1974 1975-1976"
  }, {
    "answer": "Joe DiMaggio",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Marilyn Monroe - 1954"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sandra Bullock",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Jesse James - 2005-2010"
  }, {
    "answer": "Drew Barrymore",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Tom Green - 2001-2002"
  }, {
    "answer": "Kim Basinger",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Alec Baldwin - 1993-2002"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jane Fonda",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Ted Turner - 1991-2001"
  }, {
    "answer": "Burt Reynolds",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Loni Anderson - 1988-1993"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lyle Lovett",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Julia Roberts - 1993-1995"
  }, {
    "answer": "Arthur Miller",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Marilyn Monroe - 1956-1961"
  }, {
    "answer": "James Cameron",
    "category": "Former Spouses Quiz",
    "question": "Linda Hamilton - 1997-1999"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Former Spouses Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/former-spouses-quiz.php"
}